Guide to the David Benjamin Mixner Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
David Benjamin Mixner papers
1924-2018
MS 1862
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
153.88
(253 boxes)
The papers consist of personal materials, correspondence, compiled family letters, clippings, subject and writing files, photographs, Vietnam protest memorabilia, and audiovisual materials that document David Mixner's life as a gay male, leader in the gay rights movement, author, and political consultant and advisor. There is also a manuscript of the Mixner family genealogy by Patricia Mixner Annison, David's sister; addenda/errata to the family genealogy; get well cards and photographs of David Mixner circa 1950s-1960s.
Mixner, David B.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of David Mixner, 2005-2016.
Conditions Governing Access
The papers are closed until January 1, 2031, unless researchers receive permission in writing to access them from the donor, the person holding power of attorney for the donor, or the executor of the estate of the donor. Researchers wishing to request access should email mssa.assist@yale.edu requesting specific box numbers in order to initiate the permission process, which may take several weeks.
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
Arrangement
Arranged in six series and multiple additions: I. Personal, 1946-2005. II. Correspondence, 1968-2005. III. Subject Files, 1958-2005. IV. Writings, 1989-2003. V. Clippings, 1968-2005. VI. Audiovisual, 1924, 1964-2004.
Biographical / Historical
David Benjamin Mixner, well-known activist, consultant, and author, was born on August 16, 1946, in Bridgetown, New Jersey. He graduated from Woodstown High School and attended Arizona State University (1964-1967) and the University of Maryland (1967). He became a political activist as a young adult and participated in the civil rights movement, the movement against the Vietnam War, and the anti-nuclear movement. He worked for a number of Democratic presidential campaigns, including McGovern for President, Hart for President (national co-chair), Gephardt for President, and Clinton for President (senior campaign advisor). Throughout his adult life he has actively worked with, and provided leadership for gay rights organizations, including Access Now for Gay and Lesbian Equality (ANGLE), Municipal Elections Committee of Los Angeles (MECLA), the Gay and Lesbian Victory Fund, and for organizations advocating for victims of Acquired Immune Deficiency Syndrome (AIDS). He is the author of Stranger Among Friends, an autobiography; editor of Brave Journeys: Profiles in Gay and Lesbian Courage; author of screenplays, including Dunes of Overveen and Fire in the Soul, and was executive producer of House on Fire, a film regarding AIDS in the African-American community. His consulting firm, DBM Associates, specializes in public policy, and works with individuals, businesses, and governments, in the United States and abroad, especially on projects related to AIDS and gay rights.
Scope and Contents
The papers consist of personal materials, correspondence, compiled family letters, clippings, subject and writing files, photographs,Vietnam protest memorabilia, and audiovisual materials that document David Mixner's life as a gay male, leader in the gay rights movement, author, and political consultant and advisor. There is also a manuscript of the Mixner family genealogy by Patricia Mixner Annison, David's sister; addenda/errata to the family genealogy; get well cards and photographs of David Mixner circa 1950s-1960s.
African American gays; African Americans -- Diseases; AIDS (Disease); AIDS activists; Coming out (Sexual orientation); Gay activists; Gay liberation movement -- United States; Gay rights; Gay military personnel -- United States; Gays -- Counseling of; Political activists; Political consultants; Presidents -- Election; LGBTQ resource; Clinton, Bill, 1946-; Hindery, Leo, 1947-; Mixner, David B.; United States. Congress. House. Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee; Access Now for Gay and Lesbian Equality; Gay and Lesbian Victory Fund; Great Peace March for Global Nuclear Disarmament (Organization); PRO-Peace (Organization); Transatlantic Partnership Against AIDS
- Personal, 1946-2005; Series I
  - AIDS [book of names of friends who died from AIDS], undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Annison wedding, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Astrology, 1996-2000 (Box 1, Folder 3 - 4)
  - Autograph book, 1989 November (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bankruptcy, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Biographical, 1946-1969, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Calendars
    - 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 8 - 9)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 10 - 11)
    - 1982-1989 (Box 1, Folder 12 - 20)
    - 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 21 - 24)
    - 2001 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 2004 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Clinton, Bill, "Remarks by the President to the Empire State Pride Gala", 1999 October 7 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence
    - General [mostly family], 1964-1994, undated (Box 2, Folder 28 - 32)
    - Annison, Patsy [also Patsy Mixner], 1953-1977, 1991-2003, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Coming out, 1976, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Europe, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Garlid, Dr. and Mrs. Keith, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Gay, 1987-1993 (Box 2, Folder 37 - 40)
    - Greer, Andrew, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - "Letters from Home", 1957 September-1959 Dec, 1976 Mar, undated (Box 2, Folder 42 - 46)
    - Mixner/Scott, Inc., 1983 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Nieces, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Daretown Elementary School, 1951-1960 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Family tree, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Health claims, 1993, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Journals
    - 1964-1965, 1981, 1983-1995 (Box 3, Folder 52 - 56)
    - 2000 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Marston, Patrick, 1997, undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Media appearances, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Phone books, 1996, 1998 December 31 (Box 4, Folder 60 - 62)
  - Scott, Peter, estate of, 1989-1996 (Box 4, Folder 63 - 64)
  - Speakers kit/tour, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Things to do, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 66 - 67)
  - Trip schedules, 1998-1999, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 68 - 72)
  - Websites, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Wedding, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Woodstown High School, 1960-1965 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Miscellaneous, 1965-1996, undated (Box 5, Folder 76 - 80)
  - Memorabilia, 1964-1986, undated (Box 6)
- Correspondence, 1968-2005; Series II
  Scope and Contents
  The series is arranged in two subgroups: topical and chronological. The donor has provided the following information about persons and events that are reflected in the chronological files (this information is not comprehensive):
  1994 to 1996. Battle over "Don't Ask, Don't Tell," the period when Mixner was on the "outs" with Clinton Administration, personal emails, ANGLE, the transition to hope with hope, the 1996 Presidential election.
  1996. 1996 Presidential election, DOMA (Defense of Marriage Act), 1996 Congressional elections, fund raising for candidates, Victory Fund, my 50th birthday, ANGLE, Duane Raths estate, White House letters, Marcus letters.
  1996 (September to December) - 1997 (January to February). Ken Starr investigations, "Stranger Among Friends," Defense of Marriage Act (DOMA), presidential inauguration of Clinton, ANGLE, Victory Fund, White House emails, results of 1996 elections, roles of LGBT community in elections, personal, Marcus letters, Hamsher letters, personal.
  1997 (January to June). "Stranger Among Friends," military policy on LGBT community, ANGLE, Victory Fund, Marcus letters, Hamsher letters, "Brave Journey," 1998 California Governor race, Greenville South Carolina Demonstration, personal, Digital Entertainment Network, White House emails Ken Starr investigation.
  1997 (June to December\). Clinton/Ken Starr investigations, ANGLE, Victory Fund, HRC, Marcus letters, White House emails, Hamsher letters, political fund raising, the LGBT marriage issue, military letters.
  1998 (January to June). 1998 congressional elections, the Clinton impeachment, ANGLE, White House emails, Victory Fund, personal, fund raising events for candidates.
  1998 (July to October). 1998 congressional elections, ANGLE, Victory Fund, Matthew Shepard death and protests, Marcus emails, Hamsher emails, letters from elected officials.
  1998 (November to December). 1998 congressional election results, White House correspondence, ANGLE, Victory Fund, Europe trip, personal, Leo Hindery emails, HIV/AIDS work.
  1999 (January to May). Travel schedules, personal, to do lists, Jeff Marcus emails, Leo Hindery emails, 2000 presidential elections, 2000 congressional elections, assistance to Gay and Lesbian military members, NAACP AIDS project emails, White House emails.
  1999 (May to September). 2000 presidential election, 2000 congressional elections, Leo Hindery emails, Jeff Marcus emails, Herb Hamsher emails, White House emails, DCCC Presidential Dinner in Los Angeles, ANGLE emails.
  1999 (September to December). White House emails, NAACP AIDS Project emails, Gay and Lesbian Victory Fund emails, personal emails, 2000 Presidential campaign emails.
  2000 (August to September). White House emails, 2000 elections, Los Angeles Democratic Convention, ANGLE, Mixner event at 2000 Convention, Victory Fund, congressional elections, Marcus letters, Hindery Letters, Hamsher Letters, personal.
  2000 (July to December) -2001 (January). 2000 presidential and congressional elections, the contested presidential race, ANGLE, Victory Fund, Marcus letters, Hamsher emails, White House emails, Personal emails, Bush winning the election, Amsterdam trip.
  2001 (February to May). Presidential Commission on HIV/AIDS, Jeff Marcus letters, TransAtlantic Partnership Against AIDS, International HIV efforts, Belfast Peace Conference, Out Fest MTV Award for "Dunes of Overveen", ANGLE, Victory Fund.
  2001 (May to September). ANGLE, Jeff Marcus, Herb Hamsher, Victory Fund, Dunes of Overveen, Windows Media, fund raising for candidates, 9/11 in New York.
  2001 September. 9/11 emails.
  2001 (September to November). 2000 presidential race, 9/11 event, ANGLE, Victory Fund, moving from California to Washington, DC, White House emails, fund raising events for political races, International HIV/ AIDS work, Empire State Pride Agenda.
  2001 (November) - 2002 (March). Democratic Congressional Fund Presidential Dinner in Los Angeles, the 2002 congressional elections, the Gay and Lesbian Victory Fund, Jeff Marcus letters and personal emails.
  2002 (March to July). Congressional elections, Judith Light (and Herb Hamsher), Jeff Marcus letters, letters from Jeff Trandahl (Clerk of the House), personal emails and "Don't Ask, Don't' Tell" emails.
  2002 (May to September). Bush peak years, the War in Iraq, and personal works.
  2002 (July to October). Early John Kerry, Jeff Marcus emails, early Gephardt, Judith Light (and Herb Hamsher), Mark Shriver for Congress, Congressional elections, and personal.
  2003 (January to April). Gay and Lesbian Victory Fund, ANGLE, Jeff Marcus letters, "Don't Ask, Don't Tell" efforts, Gephardt for President, TransAtlantic Partnership Against AIDS (TPAA), letters from Amsterdam, and TPAA Conference in Moscow.
  2003 (September to December). Everything from political, personal, organizational; beginning of the discussions around the presidential race, AIDS legislation, and personal emails.
  2003 (December) - 2004 (April). Email, letters, and cards from Iraq, discussions of the 2002 Presidential elections, LGBT issues, and personal.
  2004 (April to July). War in Iraq, the 2004 presidential elections, the Constitutional Amendment on Marriage, The Kennedy DSCC GLBT fund raiser in his home, Dave Koz letters, Judith Light letters.
  2004 (August to December). 2004 presidential election, the Constitutional Amendment battle, congressional elections, and personal.
  2005 (January to September). War in Iraq to Hurricane Katrina to political changes that takes place during this period. Includes letter from gay Americans serving in Iraq in different ways and personal letters.
  - Topical
    - Laughlin, Bradley
      - Greece, 1989, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Letters, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Notes/cards, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Mixner, David B.: personal papers, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 3a)
    - Political, 1968-1993, undated (Box 7, Folder 4 - 5)
  - Chronological
    - 1974, 1978-1987, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - 1992 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - 1993 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - 1994 (Box 7, Folder 10 - 13)
    - 1995
      - Jan-Jun (Box 7, Folder 14 - 20)
      - Jul-Dec (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - 1996
      - Jan-Sep (Box 8, Folder 22 - 32)
      - Aug-Dec (Box 9, Folder 33 - 44)
    - 1997
      - Jan-Feb (Box 9, Folder 45 - 52)
      - Mar-Aug (Box 10, Folder 53 - 74)
      - Aug-Dec (Box 11, Folder 75 - 90)
    - 1998
      - Jan-Feb [includes one folder of cards, 1998 Jan-Jun] (Box 11, Folder 91 - 97)
      - Mar-Jul (Box 12, Folder 98 - 123)
      - Aug-Nov (Box 13, Folder 124 - 146)
      - Dec (Box 14, Folder 147 - 152)
    - 1999
      - Jan-Apr (Box 14, Folder 153 - 179)
      - May-Aug (Box 15, Folder 180 - 205)
      - Sep-Nov (Box 16, Folder 206 - 232)
      - Dec (Box 17, Folder 233 - 243)
    - 2000
      - Jan-Mar (Box 17, Folder 244 - 254)
      - Mar-May (Box 18, Folder 255 - 267)
      - Jun-Sep (Box 19, Folder 268 - 292)
      - Sep-Oct (Box 20, Folder 293 - 298)
      - Oct-Dec (Box 21, Folder 299 - 313)
    - 2001
      - Jan (Box 21, Folder 314 - 315)
      - Jan-Apr (Box 22, Folder 316 - 343)
      - Apr-Jul (Box 23, Folder 344 - 366)
      - Aug-Oct [includes one folder of letters, 2001 Sep-2002 Mar] (Box 24, Folder 367 - 391)
      - Oct-Dec (Box 25, Folder 392 - 408)
    - 2002
      - Jan-Feb (Box 25, Folder 409 - 418)
      - Mar-Jun [includes one folder of letters, 2002 May-Jul] (Box 26, Folder 419 - 445)
      - Jul-Oct (Box 27, Folder 446 - 473)
      - Oct-Dec [includes one folder of cards and letters, 2002 Dec-2003 Feb] (Box 28, Folder 474 - 500)
    - 2003
      - Jan (Box 28, Folder 501 - 503)
      - Jan-Apr [includes one folder of cards and letters, 2003 Feb-May] (Box 29, Folder 504 - 537)
      - May-Sep [includes one folder of cards and letters, 2003 Jun-Nov; includes one folder of cards and letters, 2003 Jul-Nov] (Box 30, Folder 538 - 574)
      - Sep-Dec (Box 31, Folder 575 - 610)
    - 2004
      - Jan-Apr [includes one folder of cards and letters, 2003 Dec-2004 Jan] (Box 32, Folder 611 - 646)
      - Apr-Jul [includes one folder of cards and letters, 2004 Jun-Dec] (Box 33, Folder 647 - 681)
      - Jul-Dec (Box 34, Folder 682 - 716)
    - 2005 Jan-Sep (Box 35, Folder 717 - 757)
    - Undated cards and letters (Box 35, Folder 758)
- Subject Files, 1958-2005; Series III
  The series is arranged alphabetically.
  - Access Now for Gay and Lesbian Equality (ANGLE)
    - General, 1991-2001 (Box 36, Folder 1 - 4)
    - American Data Management, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Budget, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Checks, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 7 - 9)
    - Contribution reports, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Dinner ["a major political dinner sponsored by the Gay and Lesbian community to raise funds to take back control of the House of Representatives" - funds went to Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee]
      - Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee (DCCC), 1999 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Dinner committee, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Invitations, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - Invoices, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Labor, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - Legal, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - Major donors, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 17 - 19)
      - Press operations, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 20)
      - Program, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 21)
      - Research, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 22)
      - Table captains, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 23)
      - VIP reception, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 24)
      - White House, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 25 - 26)
      - White House advance, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 27)
      - Wrap up, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Fall program, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Finances, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Fundraisers, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - List, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Meeting, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Newsletter, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Official administrative papers, 1992, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - Presidential, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - "Slate", 1992-1996 (Box 37, Folder 37 - 41)
  - Achtenberg [Roberta] for Mayor, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - ACTION Agency, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - Africa
    - AIDS, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 44)
    - Namibia
      - Ambassador, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 45)
      - Desert trek, 2000-2001 (Box 37, Folder 46)
    - South Africa
      - Sponsorships, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 47)
      - Walk
        - General, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 48)
        - Logistics, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 49)
        - Travel plans, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - African-American AIDS Policy Institute, 1989, undated (Box 37, Folder 51)
  - AIDS
    - General, 1987-1988 (Box 37, Folder 52)
    - AIDS Action, 1996, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 53 - 54)
    - AIDS cure, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 55)
    - AIDS Foundation East-West, 2002-2004 (Box 37, Folder 56)
    - AIDS Institute, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 57)
    - AIDS list, 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 58)
    - AIDS Policy Center, 1995-1996 (Box 37, Folder 59)
    - AIDS Project Los Angeles, 1991, 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 60)
    - American Foundation for AIDS Research
      - "AmFAR Ellis Island Event", 2000 (Box 37, Folder 61)
      - Event: "Two-Steppin' for the Cure", 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 62)
    - Center for Disease Control reports, 2003-2004 (Box 37, Folder 63)
    - Cytolin, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 64)
    - Madison Project, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 65)
    - Music City Initiatives, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 66)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1998-1999, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 67)
  - Americans for Jobs and Health Care, 2003-2004 (Box 37, Folder 68)
  - Anton [Peter] proposal, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 69)
  - Baker, Jim, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 70)
  - Baldwin [Tammy] for Congress, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 71)
  - Ballot Measure 9, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 72)
  - Barnes Campaign, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 73)
  - Barrios for Attorney General, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 74)
  - Boeing, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 75)
  - Bohnett [David]
    - General, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 76)
    - Africa, 2000-2001 (Box 38, Folder 77)
    - Contributions, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 78)
    - Democratic Convention, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 79)
    - Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee (DSCC), 2000 (Box 38, Folder 80)
    - Dinners, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 81)
    - Foundation, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 82)
    - Initiative project, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 83)
    - Memos, 2000-2001 (Box 38, Folder 84 - 86)
    - New York, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 87)
    - Political, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 88)
    - Publications, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 89)
    - Speeches, 1999-2000 (Box 38, Folder 90)
    - Washington, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 91)
  - Bold New World, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 92)
  - Book study group, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 93)
  - Bosnia
    - General, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 94)
    - Application, 1998-1999 (Box 38, Folder 95)
  - Boston Freedom Awards, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 96)
  - Bradley for President, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 97)
  - C1TV
    - General, 2000-2001 (Box 38, Folder 98 - 99)
    - Ads, undated (Box 38, Folder 100)
    - Distribution, undated (Box 38, Folder 101)
    - Financials, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 102)
    - Media, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 103)
    - Presentation, 2000-2001 (Box 38, Folder 104)
    - Programming, undated (Box 38, Folder 105)
    - Staff, undated (Box 38, Folder 106)
  - Cable Positive, 1998-1999 (Box 38, Folder 107)
  - California AIDS Ride 2, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 108)
  - California delegates [list], 1992 (Box 38, Folder 109)
  - California voting, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 110)
  - Californians for Bill Press [plan], 1989 (Box 38, Folder 111)
  - Camp Sister Spirit, 1994, undated (Box 39, Folder 112)
  - Campaign for Military Service (CMS)
    - General, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 113)
    - Budgets, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 114)
    - Finance, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 115)
    - Grassroots, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 116)
    - Media, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 117)
    - Research, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 118)
    - Ritts, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 119)
  - Center for Law and Research, 1972-1973, undated (Box 39, Folder 120)
  - Checchi [Al] for Governor
    - General, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 121)
    - Bay area, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 122)
    - Clips, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 123)
    - Clubs, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 124)
    - Endorsements, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 125)
    - Events, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 126)
    - Gay press, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 127)
    - Letters, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 128)
    - List, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 129)
    - Memos, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 130)
    - Polling, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 131)
    - Woman, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 132)
  - Chicago Seven trial [subpoena, one page], 1969 (Box 39, Folder 133)
  - Clark [Wesley] for President, 2003-2004 (Box 39, Folder 134)
  - Clinton, William Jefferson
    - AIDS, 1992, 1994, undated (Box 39, Folder 135 - 136)
    - AIDS Advisory Council, 1995-1996 (Box 39, Folder 137)
    - Appointments, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 138)
    - Articles, 1991-1995 (Box 39, Folder 139 - 140)
    - Brown, Edmund G. (Jerry), 1992 (Box 39, Folder 141)
    - Bumper stickers, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 142)
    - California, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 143)
    - Campaign materials, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 144)
    - Clinton/Gore-96, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 145)
    - Convention, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 146)
    - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 147)
    - Executive Committee, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 148)
    - Finance, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 149)
    - Fundraisers, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 150)
    - Gay, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 151)
    - Glove incident, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 152)
    - Human Rights Campaign Fund, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 153)
    - "I have a vision..." speech, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 154)
    - Inauguration
      - General, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 155)
      - Mixner, David [Salute to], 1992 (Box 39, Folder 156)
    - Memos, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 157)
    - Projects, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 158)
    - Transition
      - AIDS, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 159)
      - Committees, undated (Box 39, Folder 160)
      - Executive order, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 161)
      - Follow-up, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 162)
      - Judicial, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 163)
      - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 164)
      - Pink Triangle Coalition (PTC), 1992 (Box 39, Folder 165)
    - Vietnam, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 166)
    - Welfare bill, 1995-1996, undated (Box 39, Folder 167)
    - White House Conference on HIV and AIDS, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 168)
  - Colorado, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 169)
  - Colorado boycott, 1992-1993 (Box 40, Folder 170)
  - Colorado case, 1995-1996 (Box 40, Folder 171)
  - Colorado freedom riders, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 172)
  - Colorado Project/Common Cause
    - General, 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 173)
    - Petitions, undated (Box 40, Folder 174)